Anthony Melgoza

Help Desk Technician/Desktop Support Analyst

North Hills, CA 91343
(818) 389-4320
aj.melgoza96@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/aj-melgoza

ABOUT ME

A computer savvy individual who recently obtained certifications but has always had solid knowledge about networks, computers, mobile devices, IoT, etc.. Love learning new skills and information every day. Not afraid of asking questions, doing research and putting in the hours necessary to increase my knowledge and abilities.

EXPERIENCE

Parisa USA, Northridge, CA — *Cost Assistant*

SEPTEMBER 2016 - FEBRUARY 2020

- Used Software to create a cost for the fabric that each garment required.
- Maintained and fixed any issues with the department's printers and connectivity issues with the plotter.
- Resolved issues with MS Office (Formulas) and Tuka Software.

Parisa USA, Northridge, CA — Sample Room Coordinator/Cutter

MARCH 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2016

- Managed and distributed the Sample Rooms workload in order to meet deadlines.
- Created an Excel sheet to track the amount of garments produced daily.
- Cut patterns and pass to the Sample Room to be sown.

Parisa USA, Northridge, CA — Warehouse Clerk

JULY 2014 - MARCH 2015

- Pick and package orders.
- Used our Ticketing system to create and print shipping labels.
- Keep inventory updated in our system.

SKILLS

- Network
 Troubleshooting
- Hardware/Software
 Troubleshooting
- Mobile Device
 Troubleshooting
- Windows/Mac OS
- Microsoft Office/G
 Suite
- Problem Solving
- Dependability

CERTIFICATIONS

CompTIA Network+

June 2020 - June 2023

CompTIA A+

June 2020 - June 2023

CCNA

In progress.

EDUCATION

Daniel Pearl Magnet High School, Lake Balboa - High School Diploma (2010-2014)

PROJECTS

Coding with Python 3 -Learning with Codecademy, Microsoft, and Youtube